Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=My Foxfoe Queen=
=ملكة ثعلبي=
=Episode 21=
=الحلقة 21=
That was how you tortured her yesterday.
هكذا عذبتها بالأمس.
You have sympathy for her.
لقد تعاطفت معها.
As commander of the guards,
بصفته قائدا للحرس،
you used such despicable methods to frame the Empress.
لقد استخدمت مثل هذه الأساليب الحقيرة للإيقاع بالإمبراطورة.
She is the fox demon.
إنها شيطانة الثعلب.
I assumed it was foolproof.
افترضت أنه كان منزهًا عن الخطأ.
But I didn't expect you two to be working together.
ولكنني لم أتوقع أنكما ستعملان معًا.
I was careless.
لقد كنت مهملاً.
Huang Gou'er,
هوانغ جوير,
I never imagined
لم اتخيل ذلك ابدا
you could be so cruel.
يمكنك أن تكون قاسياً جداً.
Now, the only way to lessen your guilt
الآن، الطريقة الوحيدة لتقليل الشعور بالذنب هي
is to confess what you know.
هو الاعتراف بما تعرفه.
My guilt?
ذنبي؟
Your Lordship's guilt runs deeper than mine.
إن ذنب سيادتك أعمق من ذنبي.
You personally killed all those living beings.
لقد قتلت شخصيًا كل تلك الكائنات الحية.
Your methods are far more cruel than mine.
طريقتك أكثر قسوة من طريقتي.
Do you know I was poisoned with Gu?
هل تعلم أنني تعرضت للتسمم بالجو؟
No.
لا.
All right.
حسنًا.
I'll make you talk.
سأجعلك تتحدث.
You're familiar with this, aren't you?
أنت على دراية بهذا، أليس كذلك؟
The Soul-Piercing Needle.
الإبرة الخارقة للروح.
You often use it
تستخدمه كثيرًا
to torment prisoners.
لتعذيب السجناء.
It's said
لقد قيل
that inserting it two inches into the ear
أن إدخاله على عمق بوصتين في الأذن
brings pain like thousands of ants gnawing.
يُسبب الألم مثل آلاف النمل الذي يقضم.
At four inches,
على ارتفاع أربع بوصات،
it's like a thousand arrows piercing the heart.
إنه مثل ألف سهم يخترق القلب.
Seven inches causes pain
سبعة بوصات تسبب الألم
like a dull knife scraping the heart, lungs, muscles,
مثل سكين باهتة تخدش القلب والرئتين والعضلات،
and skin being peeled off.
ويتم تقشير الجلد.
Today,
اليوم،
I'd like to test if these rumors
أريد أن أختبر ما إذا كانت هذه الشائعات
are true on you.
هل هي صادقة عليك؟
I'll ask again.
سأسأل مرة أخرى.
Do you know I was poisoned with Gu?
هل تعلم أنني تعرضت للتسمم بالجو؟
Answer me!
يجيبني!
I'll talk!
سأتحدث!
I know, I know...
أنا أعلم، أنا أعلم...
What Gu was I poisoned with?
ما هو الغو الذي تم تسميمي به؟
I...
أنا...
I don't know...
لا أعرف...
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
It's the Mother-Child Gu!
إنها قو الأم والطفل!
You're finally telling the truth.
أنت تقول الحقيقة أخيرا.
Who poisoned me?
من سممني؟
Me.
أنا.
I did it.
أنا فعلت هذا.
How?
كيف؟
When?
متى؟
When you were a child,
عندما كنت طفلا،
His Majesty often sent you glutinous rice cakes.
جلالته كان يرسل لك في كثير من الأحيان كعك الأرز اللزج.
That's where I put the Gu.
هذا هو المكان الذي وضعت فيه Gu.
When I was a child?
عندما كنت طفلا؟
You were also only a child then.
لقد كنت طفلاً حينها أيضاً.
How could you have learned how to cast Gu poisons?
كيف يمكنك أن تتعلم كيفية إلقاء السموم جو؟
Speak.
يتكلم.
Who told you to do it?
من قال لك أن تفعل ذلك؟
Want to bite your tongue?
هل تريد أن تعض لسانك؟
I see you're a loyal dog.
أرى أنك كلب مخلص.
It was all me.
لقد كان كل ذلك أنا.
Just kill me...
فقط اقتلني...
Want to die?
هل تريد أن تموت؟
Not so easy.
ليس سهلا.
Soon enough,
قريبا بما فيه الكفاية،
I'll make you talk.
سأجعلك تتحدث.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
your suspicions were correct.
لقد كانت شكوكك صحيحة.
It seems the Frozen Curse on Xiling Xuan's heart has been lifted.
يبدو أن اللعنة المجمدة على قلب شيلينغ شوان قد تم رفعها.
He's remembered everything.
لقد تذكر كل شيء.
It appears the fox demon he killed
يبدو أن شيطان الثعلب الذي قتله
was from the fox clan on Mount Yao.
كان من عشيرة الثعلب على جبل ياو.
They must have known each other,
لا بد أنهم عرفوا بعضهم البعض،
and now they're seeking revenge on the mastermind controlling the Gu.
والآن يسعون للانتقام من العقل المدبر الذي يتحكم في الغو.
If that's the case...
إذا كان الأمر كذلك...
Help me with one last thing.
ساعدني في شيء أخير.
Yaya, trust me.
يايا، ثق بي.
Xiling Heng is the one behind this.
شيلينغ هينغ هو من يقف وراء هذا.
I was young,
كنت صغيرا
but I trust
ولكنني أثق
that he never would have done that to me.
أنه لم يكن ليفعل ذلك بي أبدًا.
It must have been someone else.
لابد أن يكون شخص آخر.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Your Lordship.
سيادتكم.
Huang Gou'er is dead.
لقد مات هوانغ جو إير.
What?
ماذا؟
How did he die?
كيف مات؟
Just now.
الآن.
His Majesty declared
أعلن جلالته
that Huang Gou'er, guilty of framing the Empress
أن هوانغ جو إير، مذنب بتدبير المؤامرة ضد الإمبراطورة
and practicing sorcery inside the palace,
وممارسة السحر داخل القصر،
deserved death,
الموت المستحق
and executed him in prison.
وأعدموه في السجن.
Just as I expected.
كما توقعت.
He killed Huang Gou'er to prevent him
لقد قتل هوانغ جو إير لمنعه
from revealing any more information.
من الكشف عن أي معلومات أخرى.
The mastermind must be him.
لا بد أن يكون العقل المدبر هو.
The Mother Gu is in his possession.
الأم جو في حوزته.
Xiling Heng might return soon.
قد يعود Xiling Heng قريبًا.
We must act quickly.
يجب علينا أن نتحرك بسرعة.
This is a portrait of the Former Empress.
هذه صورة للإمبراطورة السابقة.
I feel like I've seen her somewhere before...
أشعر وكأنني رأيتها في مكان ما من قبل...
The Mother Gu.
الأم جو.
Yaya, I think I've found the Mother Gu.
يايا، أعتقد أنني وجدت الأم جو.
Yaya.
أخ.
I killed the Mother Gu.
لقد قتلت الأم جو.
Yaya!
أخ!
Yaya?
كيف؟
Huang Gou'er?
هوانغ جوير؟
You're alive.
أنت على قيد الحياة.
The thing you're looking for is here.
الشيء الذي تبحث عنه موجود هنا.
So this was your trap.
إذن هذا كان فخك.
Xiling Heng,
شيلينغ هنغ،
it really was you controlling the Mother Gu.
لقد كنت حقا أنت من يتحكم في الأم جو.
How does it feel
كيف تشعر؟
to have your entire clan slaughtered by your beloved?
أن يتم ذبح عشيرتك بأكملها على يد حبيبك؟
He was so happy
لقد كان سعيدا جدا
killing your whole clan,
قتل عشيرتك بأكملها،
hopping around like a bird.
القفز مثل الطيور.
Enough of this!
كفى من هذا!
This is all because you're controlling him!
كل هذا لأنك تتحكم به!
Once Yaya regains his senses,
بمجرد أن يستعيد يايا حواسه،
he will never forgive you!
لن يسامحك أبدًا!
Fret not.
لا تقلق.
From this day forward,
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا،
he will never wake up again.
لن يستيقظ مرة أخرى أبدًا.
Yaya...
كيف...
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
You demon,
يا شيطان
how dare you
كيف تجرؤ؟
trespass my bedchamber at night with a weapon!
إقتحم غرفة نومي في الليل حاملاً سلاحًا!
Not only have you killed palace attendants,
لم تقتل خدم القصر فحسب،
but you also tried to assassinate me.
لكنك حاولت اغتيالي أيضًا.
Fortunately, Lord Wing came to the rescue
لحسن الحظ، جاء اللورد وينج لإنقاذنا
and captured you.
وأسرتك.
Yaya...
كيف...
Tomorrow morning,
غدا صباحا
I will
أنا سوف
have you executed
هل نفذت؟
before all the ministers.
أمام جميع الوزراء.
Ministers.
الوزراء.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
I finally caught the wicked demon lurking by my side.
لقد تمكنت أخيرا من القبض على الشيطان الشرير الذي كان يختبئ بجانبي.
Thanks to the cooperation
بفضل التعاون
of Lord Wing and Commander Huang,
من اللورد وينج والقائد هوانج،
this wicked demon was captured
لقد تم القبض على هذا الشيطان الشرير
while attempting to assassinate me.
بينما كان يحاول اغتيالي.
Humans and demons
البشر والشياطين
cannot coexist.
لا يمكن أن يتعايشا.
That's right! They cannot!
هذا صحيح! لا يمكنهم ذلك!
Now,
الآن،
in front of all ministers present,
أمام جميع الوزراء الحاضرين،
I will burn her alive!
سأحرقها حية!
Burn her! Burn her!
احرقها! احرقها!
Yaya...
كيف...
Come to your senses...
تعال إلى حواسك...
Burn her! Burn her!
احرقها! احرقها!
Yaya...
كيف...
Fox demon.
شيطان الثعلب.
Your time
وقتك
has come.
لقد جاء.
♪The mortal world shifts like drifting clouds♪
♪العالم الفاني يتحول مثل السحب العائمة♪
♪So many grudges buried deep within the heart♪
♪الكثير من الضغائن مدفونة في أعماق القلب♪
♪One sword startles the soul♪
♪سيف واحد يذهل الروح♪
♪Obsessive love and hate fill heaven and earth♪
♪الحب والكراهية المفرطة تملأ السماء والأرض♪
♪A single glance back, all turns to emptiness♪
♪نظرة واحدة إلى الوراء، يتحول كل شيء إلى الفراغ♪
♪Only wind and snow accompany the fox's shadow♪
♪لا يرافق ظل الثعلب إلا الرياح والثلوج ♪
♪Life and death apart♪
♪الحياة والموت منفصلين♪
♪Tears stain the frosted blossoms cold♪
♪الدموع تلطخ الزهور المتجمدة الباردة♪
♪The soul cries blood, the heart turns to iron♪
♪الروح تبكي دمًا، والقلب يتحول إلى حديد♪
♪Through life and death, fate tests our bond♪
♪من خلال الحياة والموت، يختبر القدر رابطتنا♪
♪Tonight the lights go dark, tomorrow the shadows fade♪
♪الليلة تصبح الأضواء مظلمة، وغدًا تتلاشى الظلال♪
♪Blood dyes the vast sky red♪
♪الدم يصبغ السماء الواسعة باللون الأحمر♪
♪Only to dance with you for a fleeting moment♪
♪فقط للرقص معك للحظة عابرة♪
♪The clouds of dreams know not the traveler's chill♪
♪سحب الأحلام لا تعرف برودة المسافر♪
♪In a blink, youthful joy has gone♪
♪في لمح البصر، اختفت فرحة الشباب♪
♪One sword startles the soul♪
♪سيف واحد يذهل الروح♪
♪Obsessive love and hate fill heaven and earth♪
♪الحب والكراهية المفرطة تملأ السماء والأرض♪
♪Meeting again in the world feels shoreless♪
♪اللقاء مرة أخرى في العالم يبدو بلا شاطئ♪
♪Only a small boat sails through frosty skies♪
♪فقط قارب صغير يبحر عبر السماء المتجمدة♪
♪Life and death apart♪
♪الحياة والموت منفصلين♪
♪Tears stain the frosted blossoms cold♪
♪الدموع تلطخ الزهور المتجمدة الباردة♪
♪The soul cries blood, the heart turns to iron♪
♪الروح تبكي دمًا، والقلب يتحول إلى حديد♪
♪Through life and death, fate tests our bond♪
♪من خلال الحياة والموت، يختبر القدر رابطتنا♪
♪Tonight the lights go dark, tomorrow the shadows fade♪
♪الليلة تصبح الأضواء مظلمة، وغدًا تتلاشى الظلال♪
♪Blood dyes the vast sky red♪
♪الدم يصبغ السماء الواسعة باللون الأحمر♪
♪Only to dance with you for a fleeting moment♪
♪فقط للرقص معك للحظة عابرة♪